<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  - SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2023 Nextcloud GmbH and Nextcloud contributors
  - SPDX-License-Identifier: AGPL-3.0-or-later
-->
<info>
	<id>integration_deepl</id>
	<name>Deepl integration</name>
	<summary>Deepl integration providing translations through deepl.com</summary>
	<description><![CDATA[Deepl integration providing an translations through deepl.com with Nextcloud

This app integrates with [Nextcloud Assistant](https://apps.nextcloud.com/apps/assistant) to offer translation services We recommend to install Assistant additionally and activate Deepl as translation provider in the Artifical Intelligence admin settings.

This app also integrates with the translation API of Nextcloud server to offer translation services without Assistant. Currently this is available in Text and Talk.

To run translations and any other Task Processing tasks synchronously, run the following command in a background process (10 is the interval in seconds when the process should relaunch to use the latest php changes):

```sh
set -e; while true; do occ background-job:worker -v -t 10 "OC\TaskProcessing\SynchronousBackgroundJob"; done
```

## Ethical AI Rating
### Rating: 🔴

Negative:
* the software for training and inferencing of this model is proprietary, limiting running it locally or training by yourself
* the trained model is not freely available, so the model can not be ran on-premises
* the training data is not freely available, limiting the ability of external parties to check and correct for bias or optimise the model’s performance and CO2 usage.

Learn more about the Nextcloud Ethical AI Rating [in our blog](https://nextcloud.com/blog/nextcloud-ethical-ai-rating/).

]]></description>
	<version>1.3.1</version>
	<licence>agpl</licence>
	<author>Julius Härtl</author>
	<namespace>IntegrationDeepl</namespace>
	<category>integration</category>
	<category>ai</category>
	<website>https://github.com/nextcloud/integration_deepl</website>
	<bugs>https://github.com/nextcloud/integration_deepl/issues</bugs>
	<screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/nextcloud/integration_deepl/main/img/screenshot_assistant.png</screenshot>
	<screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/nextcloud/integration_deepl/main/img/screenshot1.png</screenshot>
	<screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/nextcloud/integration_deepl/main/img/screenshot2.png</screenshot>
	<dependencies>
		<nextcloud min-version="30" max-version="32"/>
	</dependencies>
	<settings>
		<admin>OCA\IntegrationDeepl\Settings\Admin</admin>
		<admin-section>OCA\IntegrationDeepl\Settings\AdminSection</admin-section>
	</settings>
</info>
